var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "وَإِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "And Ibrahim ",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(to) Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَأْتُونَ",
        "answer": "commit",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "latatūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَأْتُونَ",
        "answer": "approach",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "latatūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَأْتُونَ",
        "answer": "and commit",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "watatūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "ائْتِنَا",
        "answer": "Bring upon us",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "i'tinā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَأْتِيَنَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "But it will surely come to them",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "walayatiyannahum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We gave him",
        "pcklId": "462",
        "tlit": "waātaynāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "We gave [them]",
        "pcklId": "463",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "are given",
        "pcklId": "464",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We have given them",
        "pcklId": "465",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآتٍ",
        "answer": "(is) surely coming",
        "pcklId": "542",
        "tlit": "laātin",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَهُ",
        "answer": "his reward",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "ajrahu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرُ",
        "answer": "(the) reward",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "ajru",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلَ",
        "answer": "(the) Term",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ajala",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلٌ",
        "answer": "(for) a term",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ajalun",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذَهُمُ",
        "answer": "then seized them",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhahumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذَتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "so seized them",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhathumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "We seized",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذَتْهُ",
        "answer": "seized him",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "akhadhathu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have taken",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhtum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذَتْ",
        "answer": "who takes",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhat",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةَ",
        "answer": "the last",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirata",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَ",
        "answer": "the Last",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "l-ākhira",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةَ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter ",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirata",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "their brother",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "akhāhum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "But when",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "in that case",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوذِيَ",
        "answer": "he is harmed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ūdhiya",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْضِي",
        "answer": "My earth",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "arḍī",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "(to) the earth",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْحَاقَ",
        "answer": "Isaac",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "is'ḥāqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْفَكُونَ",
        "answer": "are they deluded",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yu'fakūna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِفْكًا",
        "answer": "falsehood",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "if'kan",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْفَ",
        "answer": "a thousand",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "alfa",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "save",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "921",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "922",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "923",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "924",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(of) what",
        "pcklId": "925",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "926",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "927",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "928",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "929",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those whom",
        "pcklId": "930",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "931",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "932",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّتِي",
        "answer": "by which",
        "pcklId": "933",
        "tlit": "bi-allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "934",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِي",
        "answer": "in that (which)",
        "pcklId": "935",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "So those",
        "pcklId": "936",
        "tlit": "fa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "937",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "938",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "939",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "940",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "941",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "942",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَٰهُنَا",
        "answer": "And our God",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "wa-ilāhunā",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَٰهُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your God",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "wa-ilāhukum",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah will surely make evident",
        "pcklId": "2010",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(with) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2011",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2012",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2013",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2014",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(the Way of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2015",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2016",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2017",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah will surely make evident",
        "pcklId": "2018",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2019",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2020",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2021",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2022",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah originates",
        "pcklId": "2023",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2024",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2025",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2026",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2027",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2028",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "But Allah saved him",
        "pcklId": "2029",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2030",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2031",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2032",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2033",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2034",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2035",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah created",
        "pcklId": "2036",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2037",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2038",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2039",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2040",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2041",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2042",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2043",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2044",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2045",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2046",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(are) for Allah",
        "pcklId": "2047",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2048",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2049",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2050",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2051",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "To Me",
        "pcklId": "488",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "489",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "To Him",
        "pcklId": "490",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "491",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "492",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "And to",
        "pcklId": "493",
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "494",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to us",
        "pcklId": "495",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "496",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "497",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to Us",
        "pcklId": "498",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "499",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَمٌ",
        "answer": "(the) nations",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "umamun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "who believe",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآمَنَ",
        "answer": "And believed",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "faāmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "394",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "395",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "yu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "who believe",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنًا",
        "answer": "secure",
        "pcklId": "588",
        "tlit": "āminan",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "for the believers",
        "pcklId": "788",
        "tlit": "lil'mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانَ",
        "answer": "(on) man",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-insāna",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "Then how",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "fa-annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَهَا",
        "answer": "its people",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "ahlahā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلَهُ",
        "answer": "and his family",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlahu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلَكَ",
        "answer": "and your family",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlaka",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَ",
        "answer": "(with the) People of the Book",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "ahla",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَأْوَاكُمُ",
        "answer": "and your abode",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wamawākumu",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "a Sign",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "in (the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "surely (are) Signs",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "laāyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَةً",
        "answer": "(is) surely a Sign",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "laāyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Verses",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "āyātun",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتٌ",
        "answer": "(the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "āyātun",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتُ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "l-āyātu",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدَأَ",
        "answer": "He originated",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "bada-a",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْدِئُ",
        "answer": "Allah originates",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yub'di-u",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَرِّ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-bari",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْسُطُ",
        "answer": "extends",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yabsuṭu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبُشْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "with the glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "bil-bush'rā",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَبْصِرِينَ",
        "answer": "endowed with insight",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "mus'tabṣirīna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَاطِلِ",
        "answer": "in [the] falsehood",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "bil-bāṭili",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَبِالْبَاطِلِ",
        "answer": "Then do in (the) falsehood",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "afabil-bāṭili",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبْطِلُونَ",
        "answer": "the falsifiers",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-mub'ṭilūna",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُكُمْ",
        "answer": "one another",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "baʿḍukum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "one another",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "bibaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُكُمْ",
        "answer": "one another",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "baʿḍukum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضًا",
        "answer": "one another",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "baʿḍan",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْتَةً",
        "answer": "suddenly",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "baghtatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَابْتَغُوا",
        "answer": "So seek",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "fa-ib'taghū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَلَاغُ",
        "answer": "the conveyance",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-balāghu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنُبَوِّئَنَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "surely We will give them a place",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "lanubawwi-annahum",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْتًا",
        "answer": "a house",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "baytan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبُيُوتِ",
        "answer": "(of) houses",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-buyūti",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبَيْتُ",
        "answer": "(is) surely (the) house",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "labaytu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "(has) become clear",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "tabayyana",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِي",
        "answer": "between me",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "baynī",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and between you",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "wabaynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِكُمْ",
        "answer": "among you",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "baynikum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "with clear evidences",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "bil-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَةً",
        "answer": "(as) evidence",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "bayyinatan",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَاتٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "bayyinātun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبِينُ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "438",
        "tlit": "l-mubīnu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "439",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "Follow",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "ittabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِ",
        "answer": "below",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "taḥti",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath it",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتْرَكُوا",
        "answer": "they will be left",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yut'rakū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We have left",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "taraknā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتْلُ",
        "answer": "Recite",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ut'lu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتْلُو",
        "answer": "recite",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "tatlū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "(which) is recited",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yut'lā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثْقَالَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their burdens",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "athqālahum",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَثْقَالًا",
        "answer": "and burdens",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wa-athqālan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثْقَالِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their burdens",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "athqālihim",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثْوًى",
        "answer": "an abode",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mathwan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاثِمِينَ",
        "answer": "fallen prone",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "jāthimīna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْحَدُ",
        "answer": "reject",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yajḥadu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْحَدُ",
        "answer": "reject",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yajḥadu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُجَادِلُوا",
        "answer": "argue",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tujādilū",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَنَجْزِيَنَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We will surely reward them",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "walanajziyannahum",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "he considers",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "and We made it",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnāhā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We placed",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "have made",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاهَدَ",
        "answer": "strives",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "jāhada",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجَاهِدُ",
        "answer": "he strives",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yujāhidu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاهَدَاكَ",
        "answer": "they both strive against you",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "jāhadāka",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاهَدُوا",
        "answer": "strive",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "jāhadū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَوَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) answer",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "jawāba",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَوَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) answer",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "jawāba",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "jāat",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "jāat",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَجَاءَهُمُ",
        "answer": "surely (would) have come to them",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "lajāahumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُ",
        "answer": "it has come to him",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "jāahu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرِّقُوهُ",
        "answer": "burn him",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥarriqūhu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَمًا",
        "answer": "a Sanctuary",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "ḥaraman",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْزَنْ",
        "answer": "grieve",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "taḥzan",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَسِبَ",
        "answer": "Do think",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "aḥasiba",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسِبَ",
        "answer": "think",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ḥasiba",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنَ",
        "answer": "(the) best",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "aḥsana",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "(is) best",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُسْنًا",
        "answer": "goodness to his parents",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "ḥus'nan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاصِبًا",
        "answer": "a violent storm",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥāṣiban",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمُونَ",
        "answer": "they judge",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yaḥkumūna",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "All Praises",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْنَحْمِلْ",
        "answer": "and we will carry",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "walnaḥmil",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَحْمِلُنَّ",
        "answer": "But surely they will carry",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "walayaḥmilunna",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْمِلُ",
        "answer": "carry",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "taḥmilu",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَامِلِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) going to carry",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "biḥāmilīna",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُحِيطَةٌ",
        "answer": "will surely, encompass",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "lamuḥīṭatun",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَوْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "around them",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḥawlihim",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَحْيَا",
        "answer": "and gives life",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "fa-aḥyā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَوَانُ",
        "answer": "(is) the life",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayawānu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةُ",
        "answer": "life",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayatu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the losers",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirūna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسَفْنَا",
        "answer": "We caused to swallow",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "khasafnā",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَطَايَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "your sins",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "khaṭāyākum",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَطَايَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "their sins",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "khaṭāyāhum",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخُطُّهُ",
        "answer": "(did) you write it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "takhuṭṭuhu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُتَخَطَّفُ",
        "answer": "while are being taken away",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wayutakhaṭṭafu",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْلِصِينَ",
        "answer": "(being) sincere",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "mukh'liṣīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَخْلُقُونَ",
        "answer": "and you create",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "watakhluqūna",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "Allah created",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَلْقَ",
        "answer": "the creation",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "l-khalqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَلْقَ",
        "answer": "the creation",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "l-khalqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَمْسِينَ",
        "answer": "fifty",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khamsīna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَفْ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "takhaf",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَابَّةٍ",
        "answer": "a creature",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "dābbatin",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنُدْخِلَنَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "We will surely admit them",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "lanud'khilannahum",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "they invoke",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "yadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعَوُا",
        "answer": "they call",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "daʿawū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their home",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "dārihim",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّارَ",
        "answer": "the Home",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "l-dāra",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينَ",
        "answer": "(in) the religion",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-dīna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتِهِ",
        "answer": "his offsprings",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatihi",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرْعًا",
        "answer": "(and) uneasy",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "dharʿan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذِكْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "and a reminder",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "wadhik'rā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَذِكْرُ",
        "answer": "and surely (the) remembrance",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "waladhik'ru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذَنْبِهِ",
        "answer": "for his sin",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "bidhanbihi",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُوقُوا",
        "answer": "Taste",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "dhūqū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَائِقَةُ",
        "answer": "(will) taste",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "dhāiqatu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "632",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "633",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "634",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "635",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "636",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجْزًا",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "rij'zan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْجِعُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your return",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "marjiʿukum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّجْفَةُ",
        "answer": "the earthquake",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-rajfatu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّجَالَ",
        "answer": "the men",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-rijāla",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْجُلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their feet",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "arjulihim",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجُو",
        "answer": "hopes",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yarjū",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْجُوا",
        "answer": "and expect",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wa-ir'jū",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَرْحَمُ",
        "answer": "and has mercy",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wayarḥamu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِي",
        "answer": "My Mercy",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "raḥmatī",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَرَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "surely is a mercy",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "laraḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْزُقُهَا",
        "answer": "provides (for) it",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yarzuquhā",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقًا",
        "answer": "any provision",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "riz'qan",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّزْقَ",
        "answer": "the provision",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-riz'qa",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقَهَا",
        "answer": "its provision",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "riz'qahā",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّزْقَ",
        "answer": "the provision",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-riz'qa",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "l-rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُنَا",
        "answer": "Our messengers",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "rusulunā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُنَا",
        "answer": "Our messengers",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "rusulunā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَكِبُوا",
        "answer": "they embark",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "rakibū",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَارْتَابَ",
        "answer": "surely (would) have doubted",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "la-ir'tāba",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "And made fair-seeming",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wazayyana",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيُسْأَلُنَّ",
        "answer": "and surely they will be questioned",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "walayus'alunna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأَلْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "you ask them",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "sa-altahum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأَلْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "you ask them",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "sa-altahum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْبِقُونَا",
        "answer": "they can outrun Us",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yasbiqūnā",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has preceded you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "sabaqakum",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَابِقِينَ",
        "answer": "outstrip Us",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "sābiqīna",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلَنَا",
        "answer": "our way",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "sabīlanā",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلَ",
        "answer": "the road",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "l-sabīla",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "the Way",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبُلَنَا",
        "answer": "(to) Our ways",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "subulanā",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَخَّرَ",
        "answer": "and subjected",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wasakhara",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّفِينَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the ship",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-safīnati",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَاكِنِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their dwellings",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "masākinihim",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "submit",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "mus'limūna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Hearer",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Hearer",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "(the) sky",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَمًّى",
        "answer": "appointed",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "musamman",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنَةٍ",
        "answer": "year(s)",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "sanatin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاءَ",
        "answer": "Evil is",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "sāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِيءَ",
        "answer": "he was distressed",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "sīa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّيِّئَاتِ",
        "answer": "evil deeds",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "l-sayiāti",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَاتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their evil deeds",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "sayyiātihim",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِيرُوا",
        "answer": "Travel",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "sīrū",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُشْرِكَ",
        "answer": "to make you associate",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "litush'rika",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "associate partners (with Him)",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "yush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "perceive",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاشْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "and be grateful",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wa-ush'kurū",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّمْسَ",
        "answer": "the sun",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-shamsa",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدًا",
        "answer": "(as) a Witness",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "shahīdan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "420",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "421",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "422",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْبَحُوا",
        "answer": "and they became",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣbaḥū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَرُوا",
        "answer": "(are) patient",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ṣabarū",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْحَابَ",
        "answer": "and (the) people",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣḥāba",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَدَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "and averted them",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "faṣaddahum",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُدُورِ",
        "answer": "(the) breasts",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ṣudūri",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُدُورِ",
        "answer": "(the) breasts",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ṣudūri",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقُوا",
        "answer": "(are) truthful",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqū",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the truthful",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous (deeds)",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصْنَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "taṣnaʿūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّيْحَةُ",
        "answer": "the awful cry",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-ṣayḥatu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَضْرِبُهَا",
        "answer": "We set forth",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "naḍribuhā",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَاقَ",
        "answer": "and felt straitened",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waḍāqa",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُطِعْهُمَا",
        "answer": "obey both of them",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "tuṭiʿ'humā",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطُّوفَانُ",
        "answer": "the flood",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-ṭūfānu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَظْلِمَهُمْ",
        "answer": "to wrong them",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "liyaẓlimahum",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "doing wrong",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "yaẓlimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "(do) wrong",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more unjust",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "Worship",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "you worship",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "you worship",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْبُدُوهُ",
        "answer": "and worship Him",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "wa-uʿ'budūhu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "Worship",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْبُدُونِ",
        "answer": "worship Me",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "fa-uʿ'budūni",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا عِبَادِيَ",
        "answer": "O My servants",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "yāʿibādiya",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "His slaves",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْثَوْا",
        "answer": "commit evil",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "taʿthaw",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمُعْجِزِينَ",
        "answer": "can escape",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "bimuʿ'jizīna",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَعْجِلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "And they ask you to hasten",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wayastaʿjilūnaka",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَعْجِلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you to hasten",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yastaʿjilūnaka",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبُ",
        "answer": "He punishes",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhibu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "as (the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "kaʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "biʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "[with] the punishment",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "who use reason",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُهَا",
        "answer": "will understand them",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yaʿqiluhā",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "use reason",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَيَعْلَمَنَّ",
        "answer": "And Allah will surely make evident",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "falayaʿlamanna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَعْلَمَنَّ",
        "answer": "and He will surely make evident",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "walayaʿlamanna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَعْلَمَنَّ",
        "answer": "And Allah will surely make evident",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "walayaʿlamanna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَعْلَمَنَّ",
        "answer": "And He will surely make evident",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "walayaʿlamanna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "He knows",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "they will know",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "most knowing",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "bi-aʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "know better",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "524",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "525",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the worlds",
        "pcklId": "526",
        "tlit": "lil'ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "527",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٌ",
        "answer": "any knowledge",
        "pcklId": "622",
        "tlit": "ʿil'mun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِلْمَ",
        "answer": "the knowledge",
        "pcklId": "623",
        "tlit": "l-ʿil'ma",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "731",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "732",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "733",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "those of knowledge",
        "pcklId": "832",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālimūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) do",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) do",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) do",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their deeds",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "aʿmālahum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَامِلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the workers",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "l-ʿāmilīna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(are) with",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَنْكَبُوتِ",
        "answer": "the spider",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ʿankabūti",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَنْكَبُوتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the spider",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ʿankabūti",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعِيدُهُ",
        "answer": "repeats it",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yuʿīduhu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَادًا",
        "answer": "And Aad",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "waʿādan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامًا",
        "answer": "year(s)",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ʿāman",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "those who remain behind",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-ghābirīna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "those who remain behind",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-ghābirīna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُرَفًا",
        "answer": "lofty dwellings",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ghurafan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْرَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We drowned",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "aghraqnā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغْشَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "will cover them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaghshāhumu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَغَنِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) Free from need",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "laghaniyyun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفْتَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will not be tested",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yuf'tanūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَنَّا",
        "answer": "We tested",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "fatannā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) trial",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "fit'nata",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاحِشَةَ",
        "answer": "the immorality",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-fāḥishata",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَحْشَاءِ",
        "answer": "the immorality",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-faḥshāi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) invent",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yaftarūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "invents",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "if'tarā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "the corrupters",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(as) corrupters",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْسُقُونَ",
        "answer": "defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yafsuqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفُلْكِ",
        "answer": "the ship",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-ful'ki",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقِهِمْ",
        "answer": "above them",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "fawqihim",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(were) before them",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِ",
        "answer": "before it",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "qablihi",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْتُلُوهُ",
        "answer": "Kill him",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "uq'tulūhu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقْدِرُ",
        "answer": "and restricts",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wayaqdiru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَرْيَةِ",
        "answer": "town",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-qaryati",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَرْيَةِ",
        "answer": "town",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-qaryati",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَقْطَعُونَ",
        "answer": "and you cut off",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wataqṭaʿūna",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقْلَبُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tuq'labūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرَ",
        "answer": "and the moon",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wal-qamara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "1192",
        "tlit": "yaqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "says",
        "pcklId": "1193",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَقُولُنَّ",
        "answer": "surely they say",
        "pcklId": "1194",
        "tlit": "layaqūlunna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "1195",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "1196",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1197",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "1198",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And he said",
        "pcklId": "1199",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and he said",
        "pcklId": "1200",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "1201",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "1202",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1203",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "1204",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1205",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "1206",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "1207",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And he said",
        "pcklId": "1208",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "1209",
        "tlit": "waqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "1210",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1211",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1212",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "and He will say",
        "pcklId": "1213",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَقُولُنَّ",
        "answer": "Surely they would say",
        "pcklId": "1214",
        "tlit": "layaqūlunna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَقُولُنَّ",
        "answer": "Surely, they would say",
        "pcklId": "1215",
        "tlit": "layaqūlunna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1216",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقِمِ",
        "answer": "and establish",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "wa-aqimi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "to his people",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his people",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "to his people",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his people",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "538",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "539",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "but they were arrogant",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "fa-is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "(is) greatest",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "and the Book",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "wal-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(with the) People of the Book",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٍ",
        "answer": "Book",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "kitābin",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "aktharuhum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُكَذِّبُوا",
        "answer": "you deny",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "tukadhibū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَذَّبُوهُ",
        "answer": "But they denied him",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "fakadhabūhu",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "denies",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِبًا",
        "answer": "a lie",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "kadhiban",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَاذِبِينَ",
        "answer": "the liars",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "l-kādhibīna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَاذِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) surely liars",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "lakādhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرُ",
        "answer": "you will deny",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "yakfuru",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "and disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "wakafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَكْفُرُوا",
        "answer": "So that they may deny",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "liyakfurū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "yakfurūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنُكَفِّرَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely, We will remove",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "lanukaffiranna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "465",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "466",
        "tlit": "bil-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "for the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "467",
        "tlit": "lil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفِهِمْ",
        "answer": "sufficient for them",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yakfihim",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "Sufficient is",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "kafā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكُلًّا",
        "answer": "So each",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "fakullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "Every",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "of every",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "[is]",
        "pcklId": "934",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used",
        "pcklId": "935",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used",
        "pcklId": "936",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "937",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used",
        "pcklId": "938",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "939",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "940",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "941",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "942",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "are",
        "pcklId": "943",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "She",
        "pcklId": "944",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "She",
        "pcklId": "945",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they have been",
        "pcklId": "946",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "though they were",
        "pcklId": "947",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they could",
        "pcklId": "948",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "949",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "950",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they",
        "pcklId": "951",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "(did) you",
        "pcklId": "952",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used",
        "pcklId": "953",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they",
        "pcklId": "954",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَبِثَ",
        "answer": "and he remained",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "falabitha",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعِبٌ",
        "answer": "and play",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "walaʿibun",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَلْعَنُ",
        "answer": "and curse",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wayalʿanu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَاءَ",
        "answer": "(for the) meeting",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "liqāa",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِقَائِهِ",
        "answer": "and (the) meeting (with) Him",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "waliqāihi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَهْوٌ",
        "answer": "amusement",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "lahwun",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is not",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "awalaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is there not",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "alaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيَتَمَتَّعُوا",
        "answer": "and they may enjoy (themselves)",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "waliyatamattaʿū",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلُ",
        "answer": "(The) example",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "mathalu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "(is) like",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْثَالُ",
        "answer": "examples",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "l-amthālu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "امْرَأَتَهُ",
        "answer": "his wife",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "im'ra-atahu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "امْرَأَتَكَ",
        "answer": "your wife",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "im'ra-ataka",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْلِكُونَ",
        "answer": "possess",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yamlikūna",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتِ",
        "answer": "the death",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-mawti",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْتِهَا",
        "answer": "its death",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "mawtihā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءً",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "māan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأُنَبِّئُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and I will inform you",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "fa-unabbi-ukum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّبُوَّةَ",
        "answer": "the Prophethood",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-nubuwata",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنُنَجِّيَنَّهُ",
        "answer": "We will surely save him",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "lanunajjiyannahu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجَّاهُمْ",
        "answer": "He delivers them",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "najjāhum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْجَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "But We saved him",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "fa-anjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْجَاهُ",
        "answer": "But Allah saved him",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "fa-anjāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنَجُّوكَ",
        "answer": "(will) save you",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "munajjūka",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَادِيكُمُ",
        "answer": "your meetings",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "nādīkumu",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرٌ",
        "answer": "a warner",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "nadhīrun",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلَ",
        "answer": "sends down",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "nazzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "and was revealed",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "wa-unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We (have) revealed",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "are sent down",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "revealed",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْزِلُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) bring down",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "munzilūna",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْشِئُ",
        "answer": "will produce",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yunshi-u",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّشْأَةَ",
        "answer": "the creation",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-nashata",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْصُرْنِي",
        "answer": "Help me",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "unṣur'nī",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرٌ",
        "answer": "victory",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "naṣrun",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرٍ",
        "answer": "a helper",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "naṣīrin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاصِرِينَ",
        "answer": "helpers",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "nāṣirīna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْظُرُوا",
        "answer": "and see",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "fa-unẓurū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَ",
        "answer": "Excellent is",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "niʿ'ma",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِنِعْمَةِ",
        "answer": "and in (the) Favor",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "wabiniʿ'mati",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "for himself",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "linafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "soul",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنَافِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the hypocrites",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-munāfiqīna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْكَرَ",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-munkara",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُنْكَرِ",
        "answer": "and evil deeds",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wal-munkari",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْهَىٰ",
        "answer": "prevents",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "tanhā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the fire",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارُ",
        "answer": "(will be) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-nāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "to mankind",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهَاجِرٌ",
        "answer": "emigrating",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "muhājirun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَهْدِيَنَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "We will surely, guide them",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "lanahdiyannahum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْلِكُو",
        "answer": "(are) going to destroy",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "muh'likū",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْثَانًا",
        "answer": "idols",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "awthānan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْثَانًا",
        "answer": "idols",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "awthānan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدٌ",
        "answer": "(is) One",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wāḥidun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوحِيَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "ūḥiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوَدَّةَ",
        "answer": "(out of) love",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "mawaddata",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسِعَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) spacious",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wāsiʿatun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوَصَّيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We have enjoined",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wawaṣṣaynā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوهُ",
        "answer": "and fear Him",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqūhu",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَكَّلُونَ",
        "answer": "put their trust",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yatawakkalūna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِوَالِدَيْهِ",
        "answer": "goodness to his parents",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "biwālidayhi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٍّ",
        "answer": "protector",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "waliyyin",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "protectors",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوَهَبْنَا",
        "answer": "And We granted",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wawahabnā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْهَنَ",
        "answer": "the weakest",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "awhana",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَئِسُوا",
        "answer": "(have) despaired",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ya-isū",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) easy",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yasīrun",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَمِينِكَ",
        "answer": "with your right hand",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "biyamīnika",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the Day",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "On (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "29",
        "ayah": "55"
    }
]; 
export default words;